watchmovies.com 2011-01-04

# WatchMovies.com - Privacy Policy

At www.WatchMovies.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. Please read our Privacy Statement below.

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to by email.  
Log Files

Like many other web sites, WatchMovies.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user�s movement around the site, and gather demographicinformation. IP addresses and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

Cookies and Web Beacons

WatchMovies.com does use cookies to store information about visitor�s preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

DoubleClick DART Cookie

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on WatchMovies.com

Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to WatchMovies.com and other sites on the Internet.

Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense, Valueclick, Infolinks, Kontera and others.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on WatchMovies.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

www.WatchMovies.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should read the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. WatchMovies.com privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.

Binding Agreement Your use of WatchMovies.com, including any dispute concerning privacy, is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use. By using our Site, you are accepting the practices set out in this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the changes on this page. Please check the revision date at the bottom of this page to determine if the statement has been modified since you last reviewed it. Your continued use of any portion of our Site following posting of the updated Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of the changes.
